Guide to the James Weldon Johnson Collection Files
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- "F"
  - Faustin I, Autograph letter signed, folio, Port au Prince, Empire d'Haiti, to Messrs. Dugue and Duprey, expressing his confidence in them, 1858 February 27 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Finn, Sister Agnes Eugenia, S.C.L., The Life and Poetry of Maurice C. Fields, typescript, original, bound, M.A. thesis, Marquette University, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1944 May (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Firbank, Ronald, Prancing Nigger, typescript, carbon, with cancelled title, A Drama in Sunlight, before 1924 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    Published: New York, Brentano's, 1924. Later published in England under the title, Sorrow in Sunlight.
  - Fisk University, Nashville, Tenn., "A Research Institute in the Humanities at Fisk University," typescript, carbon, February 14 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    Report from the Humanities Division to the President of the University, February 14, year unknown.
  - Ford, Nick A., "Night and a Child," poem, reproduced from typewritten copy, signed, undated (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Fortune, T. Thomas
    See: Langston, John Mercer
  - Foster, Abigail K., 1 autograph letter, signed, to unidentified correspondent, 1886 January 9 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Foster, Laurence, "Proposed Program for the College of Liberal Arts of Lincoln University," reproduced from typewritten copy, 1944 September 26 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Foster, William H., "Black Patti," typescript, original, undated (Box 5, Folder 111)
    On the singer, Madame Sissieretta Jones. Accompanied by untitled excerpts from Foster's writings on "negroes."
  - Fowler, Manet Harrison, 1 autograph letter, signed, to Mr. and Mrs. Henry Ware Eliot, 1935 May 2 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Franklin, John Hope, 3 signed letters to Carl Van Vechten, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Frazier, Edward Franklin, "The Pathology of Race Prejudice," page proofs, 1927 June (Box 5, Folder 114)
    Published: Forum, June 1927, pages 851-857.
  - Fremont, W. B., 1 autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Bonner, New York, December 5 (Box 5, Folder 115)
- "G"
  - Gannon, Margaret E., "Alumni Race Relations Council," typescript, original, signed, with a few corrections, published: Interracial Review, September 1943, before 1943 September (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Garrison, Francis J., 1 typed letter, signed, to Charles Alexander, Boston, 1905 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Garrison, William Lloyd, autograph letter, signed, to unidentified correspondent, Boston, 1857 June 19 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    See also: May, Samuel J.; Weld, Theodore D.
  - Gibbs, Harriett, 1 autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Farnam, 1896 May 4 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Giffrard, Nicholas, 1 autograph letter, signed, to D. P. Sanford, 1864 May 12 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Gilbert, Ralph Mark, Judas Iscariot, typescript, original, with author's corrections, a play in four acts, undated (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Golightly, T. J., poem, "Sing on Israel," typescript, original, inspired by the Fisk Jubilee Singers, undated (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Goode, Mrs E. C., The Education of My Grandson: Paul Robeson, Junior, typescript, original and card, corrected, undated (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Gordon, Selma
    - "Macbeth in Harlem or Shake-up in Shakespeare," typescript, original. A review of "Macbeth," produced by the New York Negro Federal Theatre Project and directed by Orson Welles in 1936, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Poems, typescript, original and mimeographed, signed, inscribed to James Weldon Weldon Johnson, undated (Box 5, Folder 125)
      Poems include "Beloved," "Dearest," and "Untitled." With an autograph note signed from Gordon to James Weldon Johnson on verso of her calling card.
  - Granger, Lester B. (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Grant, Francis Olivia
    - Term paper, "Shedding the New England Tradition," autograph manuscript, signed, with comments by Hughes Mearns, 1955 September 28 (Box 6, Folder 127)
      Also includes a typed letter signed to Miss Grant about the paper from Albert S. Davis, New York, NY.
      Gift of Miss. Grant, November 1977.
    - 31 autograph letters signed, 32 typed letters signed with 1 photostat, and 1 autograph postcard signed to Grant, documents and miscellaneous printed material pertaining to Francis O. Grant and Helene B. Grant, undated (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Grant, George Franklin
    - Letters to George Franklin Grant from miscellaneous correspondents, 1878-1909 (Box 6, Folder 129)
      Other materials include announcements of Dr. Grant's appointments to the Harvard Dental School; a check from Dr. Grant in contribution to the fund "for the Twentieth Anniversary of Harvard Dental School" in 1889; a letter of thanks for a donation to the Harvard Dental School in 1909; a letter from Charles W. Eliot to "Mr. Lewis" expressing high regards for Dr. Grant.
    - Letters to George Franklin Grant from miscellaneous correspondents and ephemera, 1882-1903 (Box 6, Folder 130)
      Includes 1 dental "demonstration" form; announcement for "Venetian Fete" on behalf of the "Temporary Removal and Permanent Building Fund" of the Dental Hospital of Ireland; Board of Registration in Dentistry certificate awarded to George Franklin Grant; an autograph letter signed recounting "resolutions of respect" following the passing of Dr. Grant at a meeting of the American Academy of Dental Science, held November 5, 1910; Letters "from persons for whom my father made artificial palates," as noted by Francis Olivia Grant, dated 1875-1889.
    - Discussion on dentistry between Dr. Biggs and Dr. Grant, typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 131)
      Gift of Francis O. Grant.
  - Greensfelder, Elmer L., Swing Low, typescript, carbon, play in one act, undated (Box 6, Folder 132)
    Gift of harold Jackman. See HJ to CVV, 04/26/57.
  - Griffin, David A., Coming Here to Stay: The Negroes in Nova Scotia, play, typescript, original and carbon, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    Accompanied by an autograph letter signed from Griffin to Robin W. Winks, Yale University, dated June 3, 1967, sent from Kentville, Nova Scotia, Canada, on the historical background of the play.
  - Groh, George, The Black Migration: The Dream, the Journey and the Destination, typescript, xerox copy, published: New York, David McKay Co., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    Gift of the Book-of-the-Month Club, 1972.
  - Guion, David W., Shingandi (Primitive African Ballet), reproduced from typewritten copy, with notes, potentially the author's, on first leaf, undated (Box 6, Folder 135)
    Gift of Mrs. Johnson, 1966.
- "H"
  - Hall, R. B., 1 autograph letter, signed, to Lewis F. Lane, New Haven, 1833 June 17 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Halsey, Margaret, 12 typed letters, signed, to Harold Jackman, 1942 June 26- November 13 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Handy, William C., 2 typed letters, signed, to Arthur B. Spingarn, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    Includes newspaper clipping noting W.C. Handy's new song arrangement for "That Love My Jesus Sent Me, Shine Like a Mornin' Star."
  - Harper, Toy Brown, 13 birthday cards to Harper from miscellaneous correspondents including Langston Hughes and Arna and Alberta Bontemps, 1965 August 16; 2 (Box 7, Folder 139-140)
  - Harris, Elizabeth, 11 poems, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 7, Folder 141)
    Poems include: "Music," "Dreams That Are Dead," "Our Tomorrow," "End of the Summer," "No Sun Without Rain," "Goodness of Nature," "The Old Village Church," "A Cabin In Waiting," "My Collected Ideas," "Books," "Lingering As It Is."
  - Harrison, Juanita, 2 autograph letters signed to Mildred Morris, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Harvey, Georgette, postcard to Mr. and Mrs. C. Douglas, undated (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Hayden, Robert E., poem, "These Are My People," typescript, original, signed on gray cover folder, with his subtitle: "a poem to be spoken", undated (Box 7, Folder 144)
    Gift of Langston Hughes, 1942.
  - Hayes, Roland, 1 autograph letter, signed, to Benjamin Lehman, 1 autograph letter, signed, to Noel Sullivan, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Haynes, Elizabeth Ross, 1930
    - List of Elizabeth Ross Haynes material, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Untitled novel, typescript, original, incomplete, unfinished novel, with author's extensive manuscript corrections, circa 1930 (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - The Black Boy of Atlanta, typescript, original and carbon, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 148)
      A biography of Major Richard Wright. Published: Boston, House of Edinboro. With a signed preface by Rufus E. Clement, President, Atlanta University.
    - ---, typescript, original and carbon, chapters 6-10, chapter 9, "Business Man and Banker," has pages 1-5 and 8 missing, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - 14 typed letters to miscellaneous correspondents, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 150)
      Includes 1 typed letter, signed, draft to "Voter," September 11, 1937, New York; 10 typed letters written in recommendation, 1936 with envelope containing miscellaneous receipts, membership cards, etc. belonging to Mrs. Haynes, 19 items.
    - Correspondence between Elizabeth Ross Haynes and miscellaneous correspondents, 1915-1953 (Box 7, Folder 151)
      Includes 2 autograph letters, signed; 30 typed letters, signed; 1 typed letter, signed draft; 13 typed letter carbons; and 1 autograph postcard, signed, dated 1915-1953, various places. Concerning invitations to speak, political activities, etc. Including her 12 typed letters, carbons, written as sponsor of the Mayor's committee on city planning, October 12, 1936-June 4,1953.
    - Autograph manuscript signed, two composition notebooks, containing notes on social, religious and educational matters used as background material for her public speeches, undated (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - Citations and resolutions honoring Elizabeth Ross Haynes, 1945, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 153)
      Includes 4 typed letters from her husband George E. Haynes, acknowledging the tributes and Mrs. Haynes' pledge certificate toward the mortgage liquidation of Convent Avenue Baptist Church, dated March 27, 1945.
    - "Women Aspire for Political Plums," typescript, carbon, essay with author's manuscript corrections, undated (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Henderson, James William
    - "America, Maker of Superman," typescript, original, with his subtitle: "A poem for a Negro verse-speaking choir", undated (Box 7, Folder 155)
      Gift of Carl Van Vechten, 1949.
    - "I Saw Jesus Down in Dixie," poem, autograph manuscript signed, with printed "souvenir" copy, Roxbury, Mass., Lester Benn, signed, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Hercule, Joseph-Domingue, 1 autograph letter, signed, to Captain Guérénaud, "20th pluvoise," written as Commander of the Black Pioneers, ordering Guérénaud's arrest, 1813 January-February (Box 7, Folder 157)
    Gift of CVV, January 1961.
  - Hernandez, Juano, The Test, typescript, original, with author's manuscript corrections, a comedy in one act, undated (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Hernandez, Miguel, The Refugee, typescript, carbon, English translation by Nancy Cunard in 1939, a play in one act, 1937, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Hikida, Yasuichi, "The Negro Through Oriental Eyes," typescript, carbon, preface to a book on the "Negro American", 1936 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    Gift of Mrs. James Weldon Johnson.
  - Hill, Ella C., 1 autograph letter, signed, and addressed to "Miss Cypher" from student Armand Friedman, in regards to a tour "Miss Hill" conducted for his class; 1 typed letter, signed, from Herbert H. Lehman; 1 autograph letter, signed, from Charles Russell; 1 typed letter, signed, from Wayne M. Faunce, 1938, 1947, undated (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Himes, Chester
    See: Cocteau, Jean
  - Hoare, E. K., 1 autograph letter, signed, to unidentified correspondent, 1854 December 8 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Hope, John, letter and resolutions commemorating Hope, typescripts, carbons and copies, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    Includes a biographical sketch of Hope taken from Charles S. Johnson's A Preface to Racial Understanding, with autograph note in unidentified hand accompanying the letters.
  - Huff, William Henry
    - From Deep Within, typescript, original, signed, A collection of poems, published: Chicago, Dierkes Press, 1951, before 1951 (Box 8, Folder 164)
      Gift of the author, 1952 September 12.
    - ---, galley proof, with author's manuscript corrections, before 1951 (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - Sowing and Reaping, typescript, original, folder has author's autograph inscription to the James Weldon Johnson Collection, March 7, 1950. Published: Avon, Illinois, The Hamlet Press. With a typed biographical sketch of Huff., before 1950 (Box 8, Folder 166)
- "J"
  - Jackman, Harold, 6 typed letters, signed, and 1 autograph letter, signed, to Harold Jackman, 1922-1939 (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - James, C. L. R., 1 autograph letter, signed, to Harold Jackman, undated (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - James Weldon Johnson Literary Guild, autograph manuscript and typed manuscript of the James Weldon Johnson Literary Guild's constitution, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 169)
    Gift of Mrs. A. F. Wilson.
  - Johnson, Charles Spurgeon, 1932
    - Autograph letter, signed, from Raymond Knox, 1932 June 22 (Box 8, Folder 170)
    - "Literature and the Practice of Living," typescript, original, signed, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 171)
      Address given at Yale University on the opening of the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection, delivered at the Frances Bergen Memorial Foundation. Includes typescript, original, with manuscript corrections and editorial markings and the galley proof for the brochure "Exercises marking the opening of the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection." The drafts are accompanied by correspondence between Anthoensen Press, Donald Gallup and others regarding the printing of the brochure (from December 13, 1949 to March 10, 1950).
  - Johnson, Grace Nail
    - Security for Everyone?, drafts, autograph manuscript, corrected and revised, typescript, corrected, and final mimeographed typescript, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 172)
      Mrs. Johnson's contribution to the 25th Century Fund's "For This We Fight" broadcast series, November 20, 1943, on the subject of the Social Security Act.
      Accompanied by other material related to the broadcast, including statements by A.J. Altmeyer, M. Albert Linton, and Robert F. Wagner.
    - ---, typescripts, original and mimeographed, corrected, with autograph leaf of notes laid in, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 173)
      Script prepared for broadcast, another version of the above subject.
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1928-1970, undated (Box 8, Folder 174)
      Contents include autograph drafts of letters by Johnson, lists, addresses, etc.; untitled poem, autograph manuscript signed, "Osmond"; "Rio Grande," a poem by Sacheverell Sitwell, set to music by Constant Lambert, typescript, carbon, with typed explanatory note.
      Gift of Mrs. J. W. Johnson, June 1967 and 1970.
  - Johnson, Hall, 12 autograph letters, signed, from to Harold Jackman, including a letter from Harold Jackman to Carl Van Vechten explaining correspondence, dated March 12, 1942, 1916-1923 (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - Johnson, Helen Louise
    - "Character of Abraham Lincoln," essay, autograph manuscript, with two explanatory notes by Mrs. James Weldon Johnson written in Ollie J. Okala's hand, dated May 3, 1969, before 1969 (Box 8, Folder 176)
    - Poems, autograph manuscript, some are original poems, others are copies of works by others, undated (Box 8, Folder 177)
      Received with the James Weldon Johnson Papers.
  - Johnson, Hugh K., War Chant, typescript, carbon, eclogue with mixed voice and strong background, 1943 March (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Johnson, May E., "Connectional President of the W.H.F.M. Society. Mrs. L.M. Hughes. A Missionary Worker," autograph manuscript, signed, poem, praising Mrs. Hughes's missionary work, with author's autograph note on verso, undated (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Johnson, Mordecai, 1 typed letter, signed, to Walter White, 1928 October (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Johnson, Pearl Rowan, Reincarnated, "in sound and dialogue," typescript, original, a one act play, undated (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Julian, George W.
    - Fowler, William J., 1 autograph letter, signed, to Fowler, 1877 December 1 (Box 8, Folder 182)
    - Childs, Mrs., 1 autograph letter, signed, to Childs, 1878 September 5 (Box 8, Folder 183)
- "K"
  - Kelly, Welbourn, 1 typed letter, signed, to Prentiss Taylor, dated May 16, 1933, 1933 April-May (Box 8, Folder 184)
    Includes Herald Tribune clipping from April 23, 1933.
  - Kibble, Florence, 1 autograph letter, signed, to Yale University Library, November 19, 1952, Chicago, Illinois, 1952 November (Box 8, Folder 185)
    Written on behalf of the Emma J. Andrews Women's Club, Chicago, enclosing a printed program for their "Around Art Corners with James Weldon Johnson," November 16, 1952
  - King, Martin Luther, Frank, Gerold. An American Death, setting typescript, xerox copy, with manuscript corrections and editorial markings, "A true story of the assassination of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.", recorded September 10, 1971, before 1971 (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - Knebel, H. A., Poor Little Rafael, typescript, carbon, signed on cover and dated June 1949, Austin, Texas, essay on Mexican-American discrimination, 1949 June (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - Kozol, Jonathan, 1 autograph letter, signed, to Laurence Sampter, 1968 July 28 (Box 9, Folder 188)
- "L"
  - LaFarge, Oliver, 33 letters received regarding dinner for James Weldon Johnson, when Johnson awarded the DuBois Prize, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - Langston, John Mercer, 2 autograph letters, signed, to T. Thomas Fortune, 1883, 1887 (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Larsen, Nella, photostats of 4 letters to Carl Van Vechten, 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 191)
    1 letter regarding Firecrakers, dated August 11, 1925; 3 letters regarding Nigger Heaven, dated September 2 and October 5, 1926, and "Monday, 6th, N.Y." Photostats from originals in New York Public Library.
  - Lasley, Cecil, poems, typescript, original, 1934, undated (Box 9, Folder 192)
    Poems include: "My Loved One Took a Visit" and "If I Could Sit and Study," written on a typed letter to James Weldon Johnson, March 28, 1934, Frankfort, Kentucky.
  - Laurence, Ann, poems, autograph manuscript, signed, undated (Box 9, Folder 193)
    Poems include "Locksley Hall (revised)," "To Fire (apologies to Omar Khayyam)," "To Harlemites," "To Fire." With a note signed to Carl Van Vechten on the third leaf.
  - Lawson, E. H., poems, typescripts, original, undated (Box 9, Folder 194)
    Poems include: "Prologue," "Ethiopian (The Wines of Palm, The Grotto of Benni)," "The Middle Passage (Serene, The Gray Mists of Morning)," "Interlude," "The Lowlands of Sorrow (Abril Fazl)." Excerpts from a poem concerning the "Negro in West Coast Africa," his journey and transition to America.
  - LeCato, Melvin, "An Education - Its Possibilities," essay, autograph manuscript, signed, undated (Box 9, Folder 195)
    Also includes poems "My Sonnet of Love" and "The Fading Horizon," autograph manuscripts, with an appended note describing his creative process.
  - Leonard, C. A., 1 typed letter, signed, to Mr. Leonard from Richard Lane Field, assistant editor at the Herald Tribune, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 196)
  - Leonard, Charles, Dear Stranger, reproduced from typewritten copy, Margaret Englander, joint author, a short story, inscribed on cover to Langston Hughes, September 23, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 197)
  - Levin, Lawrence
    - Sharecroppers Unite, typescript, carbon, with the author's manuscript corrections, a play in one act, undated (Box 9, Folder 198)
      Gift of Harold Jackman, 1957.
    - ---, typescript, carbon. An incomplete earlier version of the above, with the author's manuscript revisions, accompanied by two other typescripts, carbons, undated (Box 9, Folder 199)
  - Lewis, Katie C., poem, "What Are You Today?," autograph manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 200)
  - Lieber, Francis, autograph letter signed to unidentified correspondent, New York, 1865 December 24 (Box 9, Folder 201)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, autograph signature to proclamation regarding the pardon of Andrew Jones, with autograph signature of William H. Seward, Secretary of State, 1862 August 5 (Box 9, Folder 202)
  - Lindsay, Powell
    - Young Man of Harlem ,typescript, original, and autograph manuscript, draft, with author's extensive manuscript corrections and revisions, sometimes on versos of leaves, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 203)
      A play in three acts. Including a cancelled version of Act III and with an autograph fragment bearing Lindsay's signature and address.
      Gift of Langston Hughes, 1943.
    - ---, typescript, original and carbon. Final version, with author's manuscript corrections and additions, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 204)
      Gift of Langston Hughes, 1948.
    - ---, final version, carbon. With author's manuscript corrections and additions, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 205)
      The first leaf bears an autograph note signed by Langston Hughes, Feburary 15, 1949, identifying it as the rehearsal script used by the Suitcase Theatre.
    - ---, final version, carbon. With author's manuscript corrections and additions, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 206)
      Gift of the author, 1943.
  - Logan, James T., " Dark Rhythm: Notes for Revision," autograph manuscript, essay written after James Weldon Johnson's criticism of Dark Rhythm manuscript, undated (Box 10, Folder 207)
  - Lomax, Alan, autograph letter signed to unidentified correspondent, includes newspaper photograph clipping of man playing a guitar, identified as Lomax, undated (Box 10, Folder 208)
  - Long, Worth
    - black i, typescript, original, and autograph manuscript, with author's manuscript corrections, undated (Box 10, Folder 209)
      Gift of Ruth Stephan Franklin, July 1971.
      Poems include "Introduction," "Question," "Tears of Darkness," "Sinner Man," "black i," "Errata," "Black prophecy," "Black Majesty," "Answer." With autograph drafts of a few of the poems, folded.
    - Poems, autograph manuscripts and typescripts, original and 4 signed, with the author's manuscript corrections and revisions, 1970, undated; 2 (Box 10, Folder 210-211)
      Includes autograph drafts of untitled and incomplete poems and miscellaneous notes. Four poems are published in Mankind, May 1970, edited by Ruth Stephan Franklin, and nine poems are published in New South, July-August, 1970.
    - Poems, xerox copies, undated (Box 10, Folder 212)
      Gift of Ruth Stephan Franklin, August 1970.
  - Lucas, Robert, Tell 'Em How We Died, typescript, original, and carbon, signed on cover folder and with author's manuscript corrections and revisions, with autograph note on 1st leaf in Langston Hughes' hand, a play in one act, undated (Box 10, Folder 213)
    Gift of Langston Hughes.
- "M"
  - McClendon, Rose
    - In Abraham's Bosom, typescript, with a few manuscript annotations, written by Paul Green, play in which McClendon acted, actor's part only, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 214)
      Gift of Harold Jackman. See HJ to CVV 04/26/57.
    - Jin-Joint, typescript, a comedy sketch in pantomine, with Juano Hernandez, routine only, production in which McClendon acted, undated (Box 10, Folder 215)
    - John Henry, "Black River Giant", Episode 48, mimeographed typescript, production in which McClendon acted, 1933 June 29 (Box 10, Folder 216)
    - ---, unidentified episode, mimeographed typescript, piece in which McClendon acted, lacking 3 leaves, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 217)
    - Revolt Against God, typescript, a play in two scenes, play in which McClendon acted, 1935 May (Box 10, Folder 218)
  - McCoo, Alice White, College Incident, typescript, original, a short story, with 3 poems by McCoo, typescripts, original, with markings in an unidentified hand, undated (Box 10, Folder 219)
  - McGee, Alice, poem, "Black Man," typescript, original, undated (Box 10, Folder 220)